28tel.com 2011-09-14

# 28TEL_Make International Call For Free_From LINKWELL

        28TEL promises to manage all their business via diaphanous and moral ways, we acknowledge to inform our customers of our business principle and running method in advance(especially our price will be showed definetly.)

        Meanwhile, we take great care of your personnel information protection, we promise we won't leak out your all your information on our website to the other third company.

        Based on our guarantee to you, please read our related service items and guarantee carefully:

\----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

**PRIVACY POLICY  
**IMPORTANT — PLEASE READ CAREFULLY

        Your privacy is important to us and we take great care to safeguard the ways in which any information you provide us with is collected and used.If you would like to view, correct, complete or remove your personal information, please contact 28TEL at service@28TEL.com.   

Registration

        You need to join 28TEL to use 28TEL’s Services. By joining you acknowledge you are of legal age, provided true information and are fully authorized to sign on behalf of any group requesting the service.   

Sharing of your Personal Information

        We will not disclose your personal information outside 28TEL and its controlled subsidiaries and affiliates without your consent, except as described in this Policy Statement.

        Some 28TEL Services may be offered in conjunction with another company. In such cases, both 28TEL and the other company may receive information collected in conjunction with these co-branded services. We occasionally hire other companies to provide limited services on our behalf, such as handling mail-outs, providing customer support, hosting web sites, billing, or performing statistical analysis. Those companies will be permitted to obtain only the personal information they need to deliver the service. They are prohibited from using this information for any other purpose.

We may access and/or disclose your personal information if we believe such action is necessary to: (a) comply with the law or legal process served on 28TEL; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of 28TEL (including the enforcement of our agreements); or (c) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of 28TEL Services or members of the public.

Accessing your personal information

        You may be able to view or edit your personal information online. To help prevent your personal information from being viewed by others, you will be required to sign in with your credentials (mobile number and PIN).   

Communication preferences

        You can stop the delivery of future promotional e-mails from 28TEL and services by following the specific instructions in the e-mail you receive.

        You may also have the option of proactively making choices about the communications you receive from 28TEL, the 28TEL Services or by visiting and signing into the Site.These communication choices do not apply to mandatory service communications that are considered part of certain 28TEL Services, which you may receive periodically unless you cancel the service.   

Security of your personal information

        28TEL uses advanced security technologies and procedures to protect your personal information from unauthorised access. Your details are stored on computer systems with limited access in controlled facilities, and credit card numbers and PINs are protected with Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encryption when transferred over the internet.Your PIN helps protect your accounts and personal information, and therefore it is your responsibility to keep your PIN confidential. Do not share it with anyone, and make sure you log out before leaving the Site.   

Log files and IP addresses

        28TEL uses your IP address to diagnose our server problems and to administer our Site.
